Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America: Records of Locals WAG.234
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Records of TWU Local 100 (New York City), 1931-1978.
  - New York City Omnibus Corp.: Wildcat Bus Strike, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - New York City Transit Employees Benevolent Association, 1940-1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - New York City War Transportation Committee, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - New York Labor War Chest, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - New York Peace Association, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - New York Peace Committee, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1959-1963, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - New York State CIO: Convention, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New York State CIO: Convention, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New York State CIO: Convention, 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - New York State CIO Council, 1949-1951 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - New York State CIO Council, 1954-1956 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - New York State Dept. Of Labor, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - New York State Federation of Labor, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - New York State Industrial Union Council, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - New York State Labor Relations Board, 1950, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - New York State Motorbus Conference, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - New York State Transit Commission, 1936-1938 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - New York State Transit Commission, 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - New York State Subway Guild, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Noise, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Northern Ireland, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - North Shore Bus Company, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Oath of Office, undated, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1941-1951 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1952-1953 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1955-1958 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1959-1968 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - O'Donnell and Schwartz, 1970, 1972, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - O'Dwyer-Davis, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Office Equipment, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Offices: 210 W. 50th St., 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Omnibus Welfare Association, undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - One Unit Election (I), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - One Unit Election (II), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - One-Way Plans, 1954-1958 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - One-Way Plans, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - One-Way Plans, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - One-Way Proposals, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - O'Reilly, Gerald, 1944-1950 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Organizing, 1935, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Organizing, 1951-1954 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Organizing, 1959-1967 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Parochial Bus System, Inc., 1954-1963 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Passenger Transport, 1953-1955 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Payroll, 1954-1956 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Pensions, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Pensions, 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Pensions, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pensions, 1963-1968 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Pensions, 1970-1972 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Pensions, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Pensions (Kinzel Report), 1973 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Pensions: Correspondence from Miners, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - People's Voice, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Per Capita (to International), 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Picketing ADeserters@, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Pioneer Bus Corp., undated, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Police and Firemen: Petition, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Political Action Committee, 1949-1951 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Political Action Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Political Activity, 1940-1941 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Political Activity, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Political Activity, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Political Activity, 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Political Activity, 1956, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Political Activity, 1961-1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Political Activity, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Political Activity, 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Political Activity, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Political Activity, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Political Activity: Brotherhood Party, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Political Activity: Buckley, Charles, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Political Activity: Kennedy Campaign, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Political Activity: Lehman Campaign, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Political Activity: O'Dwyer Campaign, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Political Activity: Roosevelt Campaign, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Political Activity: Wagner Campaign, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Post Road Automobile Company, 1952, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Post Road Automobile Company, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Power Dept., 1941, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Power Dept., 1950 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Power Dept., 1952-1959 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Power Plants, Sale of (I), 1958 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Power Plants, Sale of (II), 1958 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Power Plants, Sale of (III), 1958 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Power Plants, Sale of, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Analysis, 1957- 1958 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Board of Estimate, Statements, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Board of Estimate, Transcript, Feb 20, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Board of Estimate, Goldberg Memorandum, Sep 24, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Board of Estimate, Instruments of Sale, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Mayor's Committee Reports, Aug 27, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Mayor's Committee Reports, Sep 10, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Mayor's Committee Reports, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Mayor's Committee Transcript, Sep 17, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Mayor's Committee Transcript, Sep 24, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 1 -21, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 212 - 430, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 431 - 648, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 649 - 838, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 839 - 1027, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 1028 - 1216 A, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: NLRB Transcript, pp. 1217 - 1468 A, 1959-1960 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: Opposition, 1954-1959 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Power Plants, Sale of: TWU Publicity, 1956-1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Power Supply: Report, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Private Bus Companies, 1949-1962 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Private Transport Companies, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Problems, ca.1950-1959 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Project Tenancy, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Promotions, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Prospect Independent Democratic Club, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Private Transit Companies: Contracts - Work Rules Agreements, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Public Service Commission, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Publicity, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Publicity, Mar 1948 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rican Affairs, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Queens and Nassau Transit Lines Inc., 1939 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Queens and Nassau Transit Lines Inc., 1940-1942 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Queens and Nassau Transit Lines Inc., 1950-1961 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Queens-Steinway Transit Corp., 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Queens Transit Corp., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Quill, Michael J., 1941, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Quill, Michael J., 1954-1956 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Quill, Michael J., 1966-1967 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Quill Scholarship, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Quill Testimonial: Program, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Racial Discrimination, 1962, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Railroad Division, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Railroad Marine Workers, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Rank and File Committee, 1948-1951 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Rank and File Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Rank and File Committee, 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Rank and File Committee, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Rank and File Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Rank and File News, ca.1937, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Rank and File News, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Rank and File News, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Rank and File News, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Rank and File Transit News, 1949-1951 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Rank and File Transit News, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Rank and File Transit News, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Rank and File Transit News, 1955-1956 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Rapid Transit, 1954-1955 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Rates of Pay (Bus and Taxi), 1939-1944, 1956-1957, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Rates of Pay (Transit), 1937-1963 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Reclassification: BMT and IRT Employees, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations for Employment, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Referenda, 1949, 1956, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Regulations: Transit Corporations, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Reinstatement (Davis), 1956-1957 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Religion and Labor, 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Religious and Civic Organizations, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Reorganization Proposal, ca.1959 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Research: Transit Industry (Tom Brooks), 1953-1954 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Reservoir Bus Lines, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, 1938-1941 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Resolutions, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Resolutions, 1949-1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Resolutions, 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Retirement, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Retirement, 1961, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Retirement Policy: Governor=s Committee, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - A System, 1962 1963, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Road Car Inspectors, 1960 1961 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Rockaway Extension, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Sacher, Harry, undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Safety, 1946-1959 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Safety, 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Safety, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Safety, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Safety Courtesy Campaign, undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - St. Nicholas Sports Center, 1954-1956 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Santo Defense Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Scannell, Daniel, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Scarsdale Bus Corp., 1954-1956, 1962-1965 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Schedule of Working Conditions (Transit), undated (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Schedules Dispute, 1953-1954 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Schlager, Walter, 1968-1969 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Second Ave. Line (Proposed), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Section 1, 1937-1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Section 1: Minutes, 1936-1938 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Section 2, 1937-1938 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Section 2, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Section 2, 1940-1945 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Section 2, 1948, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Section 2, 1954-1958 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Section 3, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Section 4, 1937-1940, 1948, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Section 5, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Section 5: Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Section 6, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Section 7, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Section 8, 1937-1948 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Section 9, 1939, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Section 10, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Section 11, 1937-1948 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Section 12, 1939-1949 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Section 13, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Section 14, 1937-1948 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Section 15, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Section 16, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Section 17, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Section 18, 1937-1948 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Section 19, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Section 20, 1937-1949 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Section 21, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Section 21: Minutes, 1939-1951, 1954-1956 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Section 22, 1933, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Section 22: Minutes, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Section 22: Minutes, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Section 22: Minutes, 1941-1949 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Section 23, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Section 23: Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Section 23: Minutes, 1941-1949 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Section 23: Minutes, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Section 24, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Section 24, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Section 26, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Section 27, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Section 27: Minutes, 1939-1949 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Section 28, 1937-1939 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Section 29, 1937, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Section 30, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Section 31, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Section 32, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Section 33, 1937-1942 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Section 33: Minutes, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Section 33: Minutes, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Section 34, 1937-1940 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Section 35, 1937-1940 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Section 36, 1937-1949 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Section 37, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Section 37: Minutes, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Section 38, 1948-1949 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Section 39, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Section 40, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Section 41, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Section 42, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Section 44, 1948-1949, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Section 46, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Section 48, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Section 49, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Section 103, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Section 110, 1947, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Section 113, 1951, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Section 118, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Section 126, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Section 134, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Section 204, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Section 207, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Section 210, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Section 214, 1948-1951 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Section 304, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Section 401, 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Section 402, 1941-1945 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Section 403, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Section 404, 1943-1945, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Section 405, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Section 501, 1938, 1943-1945, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Section 502 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Section 503, 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Section 503, 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Section 504, 1938, 1944-1945, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Section 505, 1938, 1944-1945, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Section 506, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Section 601, 1948, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Section701, 1939-1945 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Section 702, 1952, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Section 702, 1939-1945, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Section 703, 1936-1939 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Section 703, 1940-1942 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Section 703, 1943-1944 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Section 703, 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Section 703, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Section 705, 1942-1945 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Section 707, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Section 708, 1940-1942 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Section 708, 1943-1946 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Section 709, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Section 709, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Section 709, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Section 709, 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Section 710, 1940-1942 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Section 710, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Section 710, 1944-1945 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Section 712, 1942-1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Section 714, 1942-1943 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Section 716, 1941-1942 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Section Officers: List, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Section Rules, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Sections: General, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Sections: General, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Sections: General, 1943-1950 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Sections: BMT, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Sections: BMT, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Sections: BMT, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Sections: BMT, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Sections: BMT, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Sections: BMT, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Sections: BMT, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Sections: BMT, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Sections: Comprehensive and Eastside Omnibus Corporation, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Sections: Fifth Avenue Coach Company, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Sections: IND, 1936-1937 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Sections: IND, 1938, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Sections: IND, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Sections: IND, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Sections: IRT, 1936, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, Jan 1938-Feb 1938 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, Mar 1938-Apr 1938 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, May 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, Jul 1938-Aug 1938 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, Sep 1938-Oct 1938 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Sections: IRT, Correspondence, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Sections: New York City Omnibus, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Sections: IRT, Notices/Leaflets, Jan 1938-Jun 1938 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Sections: IRT, Notices/Leaflets, Jul 1938-Dec 1938 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Sections: IRT, Notices/Leaflets, Jan 1944-Apr 1944 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Sections: IRT, Notices/Leaflets, May 1944-Dec 1944 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Sections: List, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, Jan 1945-Jun 1945 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, Jul 1945-Dec 1945 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1947-1948 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1960, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets-I, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets-II, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1968-1969 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, Jan 1972-Jun 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, Jul 1972-Dec 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Sections: Notices/Leaflets, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Sections: Taxi, undated, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Sections: Third Avenue Railway, Jan 1939-May 1939 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Sections: Third Avenue Railway, Jan 1939-Dec 1939 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Sections: Welfare Fund, 1951-1953 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Security Risks, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Seniority, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Seniority, 1939-1940, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Seniority, 1948-1950 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Seniority, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Seniority, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Seniority: IRT, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Seniority: Third Avenue El Men, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Shop Gate Meetings, undated, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Shop Steward Conferences, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Short Line Bus Terminal, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Sick Leave, 1944-1951 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Sick Leave-I, 1954-1955 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Sick Leave-II, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Sick Leave, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Sick Leave, 1958-1961 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Sick Leave, 1962-1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Sick Leave, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Sick Leave: Statistics, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Sick Leave: Statistics, 1957-1958 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Sick Members, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Asick Transit, Delaney=s Glory@ (no author), 1941 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Signal Department, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Signal Maintainer: Training, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Signal Electricians Benevolent Association, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Social Activities, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Social Activities, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Social Security, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Social Security, 1955, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Social Security, 1957-1958 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Social Security Reports, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Society of Afro-American Transit Employees, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Sparticist, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Speeches, 1936 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Speeches, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, 1938, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Splinter Groups, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Sports, 1937-1941 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Staff, 1954-1964 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Staff: Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Staff: Memos, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Staff: Pension Plan, 1962-1968 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Staff: Union, 1952-1953, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Stark, Arthur S. (Impartial Advisor), 1954 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Stark, Arthur S. (Impartial Advisor)-I, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Stark, Arthur S. (Impartial Advisor)-II, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America: Memorandum, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Staten Island, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - AState of Affairs@ (NYS CP), 1938 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - State Senate Committee, Mar 7, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - State Senate Committee, Mar 8, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Station Agents, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Station Department, 1958-1970 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Steinway Omnibus Corp., 1938, 1940, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Steinway Omnibus Corp., 1952 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Stewards, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Stone, I. F., 1938 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Straphangers United, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Strike Fund, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Strikes, 1959, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Structure Division, ca.1959 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Structure Division, 1963-1964, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Suburban Bus Company: General, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Suburban Bus Company: General, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Subway Accidents, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Supervisory Force, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Surface Maintenance Dept., 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Surface Maintenance Dept., 1953-1954 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Surface Operation Division, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Surface Transit, 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Surface Transit, 1959-1962 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Surface Transportation Dept., 1954 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Surface Transportation Dept., 1955 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Surface Transportation Dept., 1956 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Surface Transportation System, 1937, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Sussna, E.: "Collective Bargaining" (essay), 1958 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Taft Hartley Act, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Taxi Division, 1938-1939 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Taxi Organizing, 1937-1941 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Taxi Strike, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 29)